# Hi! I'm Daryl Jane **LUZ**

**WEB DEVELOPER** 



### **PROFILE**

An Engineer by profession with 6+ years experience in data analysis and product design plus over 1 year of experience as a web developer specializing in front-end design for website development. Worked on a variety of projects, including front and back end development.

#### **EDUCATION**

- Full-stack Web Developer (March 2023)
   Kodego Bootcamp
- BS in Electronics Engineering (Mar. 2010) Xavier University, Ateneo de Cagayan

#### **PROJECT EXPERIENCE**

# **Kodego - Capstone Project (BEST CAPSTONE)** *Craft Factory - An E-commerce Website*

- Tools used: Blade, Laravel, Livewire, PHP, XAMPP, Bootstrap, MySQL, Messenger API, Email API
- Led the team in creating the website from scratch, from planning, designing to coding.

#### **Kodego - MP2 Project**

We-Learn - An E-learning Website

- Tools used: Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Canva, Javascript, Github, Messenger API, Email API
- Provided the design and front-end codes during web development.

#### Portfolio Website

Web Developer Portfolio

- Tools used: React JS, Next JS, Tailwind CSS
- Build my personal portfolio showcasing my frontend dev skills.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- Front-end Coding
- Sitemap/Wireframe/ERD
- Responsive Design
- Version Control/Git
- Debugging & Testing
- Bootstrap
- React JS
- PHP/Laravel
- MySQL
- API

#### **Address**

Compostela, Cebu, Philippines

#### **Email**

djluz.fswebdev@gmail.com

#### **Preferred Location**

Cebu or Work From Home Setup

## Website (Portfolio)

<u>djluz.website</u>

**Social Media** 

<u>@daryljaneluz</u>

**Github** 

https://github.com/Djluz

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To seek a position where I can contribute and enhance my skills & knowledge acquired, and excel while giving my best to the company I work for.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Freelance Virtual Assistant January 2022-Present

- Managed Emails, set appointments, booked travels & accommodations and created various WordPress projects for clients.
- Constant communication with client/s and the team to develop mutual trust and build rapport.
- Collaborated with teams to resolve problems, prioritize needs, define content criteria, or select solutions.

## Online Shop & Cake Shop Owner October 2018-October 2022

- Manages online shop in e-commerce platforms (Shopee & Lazada) by way of updating inventory, scheduling deliveries & immediate response to customers' queries.
- Enhanced my creativity and attention to detail through producing beautiful and unique cake designs requested by clients..

## Technical Engineer at Minebea Mitsumi Inc. *July 2011-January 2018*

- Conducted experiments, data analyses and brainstorm with the core team (Japan & Local).
- Attended Japan Trainings (Yamagata, Japan) to launch new product models for mass production.
- Team Lead for automotive product model's Process
   Failure Mode Effect Analysis and assisted in IATF 16949
   Re-certification.
- Mastered critical thinking skills & teamwork.